apkreleases.com 2015-12-25

# Privacy Policy - APK Releases

_This privacy document was last revised on February 20, 2014._

At APK Releases, your privacy is our number one concern. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by APKReleases.com (The Site) and how it is used.

## Personal Information

APKReleases.com does not require any information which can be traced back to, and identify a unique user. Certain features of the site however (like comments for example) , do require a valid [email](http://www.apkreleases.com/tag/email/) address to verify legitimate users. We guarantee that the information provided to The Site would never be used for any other purpose.

## Log Files

Like many other web sites, APK Releases makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. All of the data recorded is not linked to any information that could personally identify a unique individual.

## Cookies and Web Beacons:-

This site itself, does not use any cookies to store information. Third party service providers however may store information on your computer. Refer to the following sections to understand what information is collected and how to opt out of the process.

## \- DISQUS Comments

APK Releases uses Disqus Comments system to collect and manage comments on the blog. Disqus, as a third party service provider uses cookies to maintain your Disqus profile. You may easily opt out of the process by not posting a comment on the site.

## \- DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on APKReleases.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to APKReleases.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

## Advertising Partners:-

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

## 1\. Google AdSense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on APKReleases.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

APKReleases.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. APKReleases.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Note:** APKReleases.com also uses **Kontera,[InfoLinks](http://www.apkreleases.com/tag/infolinks/), PulsePoint, TribalFusion** as other alternative ad networks. In the past, The Site has used **Technorati Media, BuySellAds** and several other publisher ad networks.

## External Sites

APK Releases may often link to content on external websites. The Site has no control over the nature of content on these external websites or their policies regarding information and privacy. For further information, please review the individual policies of these websites.

## Policy Changes

APK Releases reserves the right to make any (major or minor) change to this privacy document without any prior warning. The site may or may not notify the users regarding any change made to the policy, however we will always reflect the latest policies and their effective dates in this document.

## Further Information

If you require any further information about the policy or clarification on any of the clauses, please feel free to contact haris[at]harisnadeem[dot]com.
